A Guide to the Sol and Virginia Wrenn family papers, 1815-2020
Library of Virginia
- Sol Wrenn Papers, 1935-2020., Extent: 12 boxes. (Box 10-21)
  - Randolph-Macon College, 1938-2006., 1 box (Box 12)
    - Phi Kappa Sigma, Tau Chapter, Randolph-Macon College, membership directory, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - University of Southern California, 1940-2009., 1 box (Box 12)
    - University of Southern California admission credit summary-registration permit, 3 August 1940 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - University of Southern California Bulletin, 1 June 1941 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - El Rodeo, University of Southern California yearbooks, 1941, 1942 (see box 36) (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - For Whom the Bell Tolls screen adaptation by Sol Wrenn (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Documentary, contributions by Stuart Legg and Raymond Spottiswood, edited by John Grierson (Canada) (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Southern California Daily Trojan, 8-9 December 1941 (transferred to the newspaper collections) (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Los Angeles Times and Los Angeles Evening Herald and Express, 25 February 1942 (transferred to the newspaper collections) (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Photographs of Los Angeles and of Lake Tahoe, 7 December 1941 (LA), June 1942 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - In Motion, University of Southern California School of Cinema-Television, Summer 1999 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Herb Farmer obituary and related articles from USC Cinematic Arts website, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - USC School of Cinematic Arts alumni directory, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Graduate School, 1970-1974., 1 box (Box 13)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University, educational psychology 607, paper--Case Study of an Undirected Classroom, 6 January 1970 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Guide for Master's Theses, Projects, and Graduate Record Examinations, Virginia State CollegeSeptember 1971 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Sol Wrenn--master's degree correspondence, December 1972 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - History of Water Transportation in Virginia, a slide-tape presentation, project for master's degree in education from Virginia State College, 6 May 1973 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Sol Wrenn--high school, college, and graduate school transcripts, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - USS Planter and Naval service, 1943-2001., 3 boxes (Box 13-15)
    - The War Comes to US: The Inside Story in Pictures, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - The Ships and Aircraft of the U.S. Fleet, 1942 (war edition), 1950 (6th edition) (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Sol Wrenn commission, 15 May 1943 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Training Film Producer's Manual, January 1943 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - The Hoist NavTraScol (Naval Training School) class book, July 1943 (see box 28) (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - A letter from--Naval Training School, Harvard University, ca. 1943 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Cruise of the USS Planter, 1944-1946 (see also box 32) (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - USS Planter diary, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Sol Wrenn correspondence and papers, 1944-1945 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Sol Wrenn certificate of satisfactory service, 11 August 1946 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - USS Planter roster, 1944-1946 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - USS Planter communications, 1944-1945 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - USS Planter miscellaneous documents, 1944-1945 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - U.S. Navy miscellaneous documents, 1941-1945 (see also box 32) (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - The Daily Planter, 23 May 1944 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - The Planter Punch, 15 August, 13 October 1945 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Nob News, 19 October 1945 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Rouge-Midi, 9 September 1944 (transferred to the newspaper collections) (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Boston Globe, 8 January 1945 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - La Estrella de Panema, 13 April 1945 (transferred to the newspaper collections) (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Okinawa map, 1945 (see box 35, folder 2) (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Typhoons in Okinawa area, 1945 (see box 35, folder 2) (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Photograph--Ensign Sol Wrenn, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - World War II scrapbook--France, Italy, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Photographs of USS Planter (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Photographs of the USS Planter in Okinawa, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Photographs of the USS Planter--naval personnel and scenes (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Photographs and postcards of Toulon, France, including the French fleet, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Postcards of Toulon, France (postwar) (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - U.S. Navy photograph of Normandy, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - USS Planter reunion--Fort Myers, Florida, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - USS Planter reunion--Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - USS Planter reunion--Virginia Beach, Virginia, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - USS Planter reunion--Newport, Rhode Island, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - USS Planter reunion photographs--Newport, Rhode Island, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - USS Planter reunions--slides, 1986-1989 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - USS Planter reunion--Virginia Beach, Virginia (not held), 1992 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - USS Planter reunion--Virginia Beach, Virginia, 1994 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - USS Planter reunion--Virginia Beach, Virginia, 1994 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - USS Planter reunion--Washington, D.C., 2001 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - USS Planter reunion--Washington, D.C., 2001 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - USS Planter reunions--lists, name tags (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - USS Planter reunions--Sol Wrenn correspondence with former shipmates, 1986-2000 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - USS Planter reunions--50th anniversary calendar, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - USS Planter reunions--miscellaneous photographs (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - USS Planter reunions--miscellaneous papers (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Sol Wrenn Naval Reserve commission, 29 October 1948 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Naval Reserve official correspondence, 1950-1981 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Sol Wrenn governor's commissions as aide-de-camp, 1950-1982 (see also box 35, folders 3-4) (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Navy and Naval Reserves articles and clippings, 1952-1985 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Naval Reserve miscellaneous papers and photographs (see also box 35, folder 5) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Film Production Service, Virginia State Department of Education, 1946-1990., 2 boxes (Box 15-16)
    - Sol Wrenn correspondence and papers, 1946-1990 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Sol Wrenn notes (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Sol Wrenn retirement, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Sol Wrenn retirement--Public Education in Virginia article, Winter 1986 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Sol Wrenn retirement photographs (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Film Production Service history, ca. 1985 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Film Production Service policies and procedures (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Film Production Service committees meeting minutes, 1949-1950 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Cooperation between the State Department Education and the Motion Picture Service of the U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Film Production Service assistant supervisor job description, 16 Augut 1973 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Films Produced or Distributed by the Virginia Department of Education/Film Production Service, 1946-1984 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Educational Motion Pictures for Virginia's Public Schools: a Paper Dealing with the Virginia Department of Education Film Distribution System, December 1975 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Educational Motion Pictures for Virginia Public Schools, March 1946 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Educational Motion Pictures and Filmstrips on Virginia, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Educational Motion Pictures and Filmstrips on Virginia, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Educational Motion Pictures and Filmstrips, 1961, 1965, 1971, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Educational Motion Pictures and Filmstrips for Virginia Schools, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Educational Motion Pictures and Filmstrips for Virginia Schools, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Motion Pictures about Virginia, undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Virginia 1985 Film Production Guide, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - A Guide for Using the Film the Elementary School (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Waterway to the West, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Film and filmstrip inventory (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Media usage analysis, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Specialized equipment inventory, 1 July 1981 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Virginia School Reports, 1871-1872 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Acts of Assembly Act for production of motion picture films, 1945 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Superintendent of Public Education educational film production and use, 1946-1947 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Centennial News Letter (2 issues) November 1962, July 1963 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Public Education in Virginia (2 issues), Winter 1966, Fall 1967 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - A Brief History of the Early Film Program for Virginia's Public Schools, 1938-1945, VEMA Journal, October 1986 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - State Prepares Color-Sound Film on School Bus Operation, Wheels of Progress, January 1950 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - About Film and Four Letter Words (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Articles, 1936 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Articles, 1948-1950 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Articles, 1951-1953 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Articles, 1955, 1960, ca. 1950s (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Articles, 1962-1970 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Articles, 1975-1983 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Articles, undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Film Production Service photographs (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Former Department of Education employees (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous papers and notes (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - University Film and Video Association (UFPA, UFA & UFVA), 1947-2011., 5 boxes (Box 16-20)
    - Sol Wrenn University Film and Video Association (UFVA) certificate, 12 August 1983 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - University Film Producers Council report, 17-21 August 1947 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - University Film Producers Association (UFPA) financial Report on Examination, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - University Film Association (UFA) financial Report on Examination, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - UFA financial Report on Examination, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - UFA reports on grants, 28 December 1978 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - UFA treasurer's and financial reports, 9 August 1979 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - UFVA membership brochure (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - UFA membership directory, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - UFA membership directory, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - UFA membership directory, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - UFVA membership directory, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - UFVA membership directory and supplement (1985), 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - UFVA membership directory, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - UFVA membership directory, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - UFVA membership directory, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - UFVA membership directory, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - UFVA membership directory, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - UFVA membership directory, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - UFVA membership directory, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - UFVA membership directory, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - UFVA membership directory, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - UFVA membership directory, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - UFVA membership directory, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - UFVA membership directory, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - UFVA membership directory, 2008-2009 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - UFVA membership directory, 2010 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - UFVA membership directory, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - UFPA meeting, University of Iowa, Iowa City, Iowa--Sol Wrenn's recollection of first meeting, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - UFPA conference, Penn State, State College, Pennsylvania, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - UFPA conference, Purdue University, Lafayette, Indiana, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - UFPA conference, College of William and Mary, Williamsburg, Virginia (hosted by the Virginia State Department of Education), 1960 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - UFPA conference, University of Miami, Miami, Florida, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - UFPA conference, Oregon State University, Corvallis, Oregon, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - UFA conference, University of Washington, Seattle, Washington, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - UFA conference, Dartmouth College, Hanover, New Hampshire, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - UFA conference, Rochester Institute of Technology, Rochester, New York, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - UFA conference, University of Maryland, College Park, Maryland, 1977. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - UFA conference, University of Southern California, Los Angeles, California, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - UFA conference, University of South Dakota, Vermillion, South Dakota, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - UFVA conference, Southern Illinois University, Carbondale, Illinois, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - UFVA conference, North Texas State University, Denton, Texas, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - UFVA conference, James Madison University, Harrisonburg, Virginia, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - UFVA conference, University of Southern California, Los Angeles California, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - UFVA conference, University of Ohio, Athens, Ohio, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - UFVA conference, Loyola-Marymount University, Los Angeles, California, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - UFVA conference, Montana State University, Bozeman, Montana, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - UFVA conference (includes University Film and Video Foundation), Ithaca College, Ithaca, New York, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - UFVA conference, Oregon State University, Corvallis, Oregon, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - UFVA conference, Florida State University, Sarasota, Florida, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - UFVA conference, Temple University, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - UFVA conference, Montana State University, Bozeman, Montana, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - UFVA conference, Keene State College, Keene, New Hampshire, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - UFVA conference, Chapman University, Orange, California, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - UFVA conference, University of Wisconsin-Oshkosh, Oshkosh, Wisconsin, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - UFVA conference, University of Wisconsin-Oshkosh, Oshkosh, Wisconsin--photographs, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - UFVA conference, North Carolina School of the Arts, Winston-Salem, North Carolina, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - UFVA conference, North Carolina School of the Arts, Winston-Salem, North Carolina--photographs (including photographs of the University Film and Video Foundation), 1998 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - UFVA conference, Emerson College, Boston, Massachusetts, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - UFVA conference, Kodak Headquarters, Rochester, New York, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - UFVA conference, University of South Carolina, Columbia, South Carolina, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Map of UFVA conferences, 1947-1997 (see box 41, folder 7) (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - UFPA receipt books (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - UFPA tie tacks, pins, and cuff links (see box 37) (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - UFVA 40th anniversary--list of old time UFPA members, 2 March 1987 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - UFVA 40th anniversary correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - UFVA 40th anniversary papers, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Syracuse University overseas project--Sol Wrenn, 1950-1952 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - UFPA/Syracuse University overseas project reunion correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Univrsity Film and Video Foundation (UFVF) papers, 1978-2003, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - UFVF--Eastman School, Halifax County, North Carolina, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - UFPA, UFA, UFVA miscellaneous papers (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - UFPA miscellaneous photographs (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - UFPA Digest, January 1956, October 1957, January 1958 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Digest of the University Film and Video Association, September, December 1986, February 1987 (40th anniversary conference) (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Digest of the University Film and Video Association, 1988-1998 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - University Film Producers Association Journal re: meeting at Ithaca, New York, March 1949 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Journal of the University Film Association, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Journal of the University Film Association, Fall 1978 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Journal of Film and Video, Spring 1986 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Journal regarding nomenclature issue, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - UFA, UFVA Monograph No. 2: Glossary of Film Terms, Summer 1978, revised 1986 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - UFA Monograph No. 4: The Influence of the World Cinema Heritage on the Education and Training of Film/Television Directors and Communicators, Fall 1979 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Motion picture organizations and publications, 1950-1997., 1 box (Box 20)
    - Council on International Non-theatrical Events (CINE) papers, 1996-1997, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - (Society of Motion Picture and Television Engineers) SMPTE Journal: 1982 SMPTE Directory for Members, part II, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - STMPE Journal: Special Issue Progress '82, April 1983 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - American Cinematographer Hand Book and Reference Guide, 1950 (see box 32) (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - International Film Foundation, Inc., 1972 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Women Make Movies catalog, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Organization memberships and hobbies, 1936-2007., 2 boxes (Box 20-21)
    - Richmond Weather Watch, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - American Meteorological Society, Central Virginia Chapter, papers 1985-1991, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - American Meteorological Society, Central Virginia Chapter, Sol Wrenn observations, 1985-1987 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - American Meteorological Society, Central Virginia Chapter, Sol Wrenn observations, 1988-1990 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - American Meteorological Society, Central Virginia Chapter, Sol Wrenn observations, 1991-1993 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - American Meteorological Society, Central Virginia Chapter, Sol Wrenn observations, 1994-1996 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - American Meteorological Society, Central Virginia Chapter, Sol Wrenn observations, 1997-1999 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - American Meteorological Society, Central Virginia Chapter, Sol Wrenn observations, 2000-2002 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - American Meteorological Society, Central Virginia Chapter, Sol Wrenn observations, 2003-2005 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - American Meteorological Society, Central Virginia Chapter, Sol Wrenn observations, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Natural resources and weather, 1973, 1980, undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - What Will the Weather Be? A Folk Weather Calendar, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Westover Ruritan Club, 1967-1994 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Downing Ruritan Club handbook, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Richmond Astronomical Society membership lists, 1958-1988 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Eclipse of the sun, 7 March 1970 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Boy Scout membership cards, 1936, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Stamps and Stamp collecting, Richmond Stamp Club, 1937-1981 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Canals and Navigation Society prints (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - The Virginia Chapter: The First 40 Years, The Nature Conservancy, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Celebrating the American Earth: A Tribute to Ansel Adams, The Wilderness Society (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, 1934-2008., 1 box (Box 21)
    - What's Next, Pizarro?, Raymond and Kenneth Dyches; The Wilderness Road, Robert L. Kinkaid (see box 29) (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Official Pictures in Color: A Century of Profress Exposition, 1934 (see box 35, folder 6) (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Kodak publications--A 100 Year Start on Tomorrow, and Creators of the Dream Machine, 1980, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - WRVA the First Forty Years, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Photography: The 150th Anniversary, Sky, June 1989 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Clippings on the 1938 and 1942 Duke University football teams, 1988, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - The Scientific Hand Calculator: Putting Space in a Small Package (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1957-1993, undated (see also box 31) (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Photographs--Sol Wrenn, ca. 1930s (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Photographs--home, Lake Page, 2007-2008, undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Photographs--Bon Air, Richmond, 1975, 1980, undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Photographs--New York, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Photographs--travel, 1940-1943 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Photographs--California: Golden Gate Exposition, Lake Tahoe, Mount Whitney, Sequoia Park, Sierra Mountains, 1942, 1979, 1987, undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Photographs--California: Yosemite, 1942, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Photographs--Arizona, Oregon (Crater Lake), Wyoming (Grand Teton Mountains), 1991, undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Photographs--unidentified (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Virginia Wrenn Papers, 1921-2017., Extent: 5 boxes. (Box 21-25)
  Series III: Virginia Wrenn Papers, 1921-2017, consisting of autograph books, biographies, certificates, clippings, correspondence, essays, magazines, medals, photographs, plaques, poetry, ribbons, scrapbooks, and other papers pertaining to Virginia Wrenn's youth and education; her work as an author and a poet, including as a member of the Richmond Story League and sponsor of the Jolly Wrenn Bards; the Crestwood Farms Garden Club and gardening; and her time as Mrs. Virginia and a contestant for Mrs. America. Papers also include greeting and Christmas cards that she designed.
  - Personal papers, 1938-2017., 1 box (Box 21)
    - Virginia Elizabeth Wimer Wrenn autobiography, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Virginia Wrenn funeral bulletin, 30 March 2017 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Virginia Wimer home, Swoope, Augusta County, Virginia (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Autograph book, 1938-1939 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Engagement announcement clippings, 1948-1949 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - P. E. O. (Philanthropic Educational Organization) record (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Papers, 1955, undated (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Churchville High School, 1939-2008., 1 box (Box 21)
    - Churchville High School picture, ca, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Churchville High School reunions scrapbook, 1939-2008 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Churchville High School reunions scrapbook photographs, 1991, 2001-2002, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Churchville High School reunions scrapbook alumni lists, 1999. 2002, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Churchville High School reunions scrapbook reunion information, 1991-2003 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Churchville High School reunions scrapbook T-Bone Tooter's, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Churchville High School reunions scrapbook miscellaneous papers, 2001, 2008, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Churchville High School reunions--images and cassette of song, undated (see box 31 and box 43, folder 2) (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Writing, story-telling, and poetry, 1973-2013., 3 boxes (Box 22-24)
    - Richmond Story League programs, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Richmond Story League programs and directories, (1982-1983)-(1993-1994) (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Richmond Story League programs and directories, (1994-1995)-(2012-2013) (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Richmond Story League annual luncheon, 1974, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Richmond Story League history, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Richmond Story League Ginny Wrenn's Gems Workshop: Gems of the Richmond Story League, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Richmond Story League papers, 1978-2013 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Richmond Story League photographs, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 16)